What is this again?
Don't you have other things to do
besides this?
Sorry sir, this lane is closed temporarily.
You can turn around through the other way.
Please understand.
Go on.
But I'm gonna be late!
This is a very important order package.
If this package is not delivered on time...
Who do you think will be responsible?!
Geez, Okay. Just be quick, all right?
You can pass.
Come on.
What a really bad day...
Rough morning. What more...
Dammit!
Dammit!!
As if anything else
could go worse!
"TRAIN TO BUSAN"
Sunbaenim,
statistical data companies showed
abnormal stock market returns.
What we need is to take action
as soon as possible.
In order to secure our position in this stock market.
Yes.
Thank you for the instructions.
I will do it as soon as possible.
Yes.
It will be done as you wish.
Yeah yeah.
Have a nice day!
Come into my office.
Yes, director?
Secure all of our assets in the stock market.
All of them?
Yes.
Is it not too risky to do this?
We could still maintain our first assets...
and wait if something better comes...
Mr. Kim...
Yes sir?
You just do what I tell you to do.
We must be careful of the
possibilities that may happen.
Yes sir.
One more thing Mr Kim...
What's the popular gift for kids nowadays?
Forget it. You really can't be a good dad to Soo-an.
You didn't even attend her recital.
You know I'm busy at work.
She can stay here in Seoul with me.
Just send her here in Busan!
You've already broke your promises!
How many times have you told her
you'll come come with her.
Can you keep it just this once?
Yes, I promise we'll go there soon!
I don't believe you.
Take my word for it.
Anyway you have to keep your promise.
Our daughter is tired
of your broken promises.
Nevermind, talk to you later.
You know that its her birthday tomorrow right?
I know!
Let me help you with that.
Thank you.
How is she?
She's playing in her room.
When are we going there?
Don't know when.
Mom doesn't talk to Dad, huh?
I have to go. Dad is here.
Soo-ann why are you awake?
I can't sleep
Your mom and I talked.
I promised your mom we'd go together.
But before that there are things
I have to do...
Soo-an you have to be patient.
Open it.
You thought I forgot?
Happy birthday.
Open it now.
What's wrong...
Don't you like it?
Could you replace this one?
Maybe we could?
What do you want?
Busan.
I want to go to mom at Busan.
Tomorrow.
Yeah, just wait.
We'll certainly go there once
your dad is done with work.
No.
Tomorrow.
You always make promises you can't keep.
We have to go tomorrow
no matter what.
Are you not tired of working
all the time?
Grant my wish for once.
What did your daughter said?
She wants us to have a vacation.
Does she want to go to Busan?
Yes.
Since the divorce, she loves you both less.
She misses the times when her parents
were still together.
As if she wants her family reunited again.
There's nothing wrong with your family
being reunited again.
Try it this time so your family
is back together again.
Ma...
I do not want to talk about it...
Let it be the past...
Okay.
Don't be too busy with work...
Sometimes you should not always focus on work.
Soo-an is growing up.
She also needs you.
Take care of your family, especially Soo-an.
Come on Soo-an, cheer up!
It's okay, continue singing...
Please give a round of applause
to Soo-an!
Okay.
Yes...ma..
No.
I'm with dad.
Yeah, see you there...
Hey Soo-an, isn't your song
finished yet?
How did you know?
You weren't there.
Dad always know what you've been doing.
You got nervous right? Am I right?
Yes...
Okay.
You know you have to finish
that song.
When you start something.
You should finish it no matter what.
Always remember that.
Ahh... that was close.
What's going on?
It's like raining ashes.
It looks like a big fire.
Hopefully there were no casualties.
All departing passengers, kindly board the train now
as this train is now ready to depart for Busan.
Excuse me, where is the south station?
Ah, South station,
you need to go that way..
Thank you.
Hold on, hold on...
Your scarf...
Please rest during this trip.
Good.
Wow, Jin-Hee is here.
What do you mean,
I'm coming with you guys.
I'm your cheerleader.
How are you guys doing?
Good.
Finally, something fresh for the eyes!
Finally!
Hey, it's rude to take something
that's not yours.
You really hate to share.
Hey, maybe if we were lovers
you're gonna share...
I might even share my bed with you...
Wow, very tempting!
Share with her! Share with her!
You want some?
Oh my God!
Don't eat too much eggs...
You'll be passing gas later...
Here take it.
- Eat...
- No thanks.
- Sunbaenim, are you on the train?
- Yes, we're on the train.
Stop thinking about work...
We'll take care of it.
Okay.
We will discuss it again after this holiday.
He manages the company well.
- See you later.
- Good.
- This is not happening...
Please don't let this happen!
- Choi Gyo..
- Yes.
- Can you please check lavatory?
- Okay.
- I'd been waiting to go to the lavatory.
- It's occupied.
Ask what's happening in there.
I'm afraid something happened to him.
Yes, he's been there a long time.
Well, I will check ...
Please wait a moment...
Sir?
Do you have a ticket?
Sir, do you have a ticket?
If you don't, we need to drop
you off on the next station.
Everyone is dead.
- Everyone is dead.
- What?
Hey little girl!
What are you doing here?
I think there are zombies hiding here.
There are no zombies in modern times like this.
Sir, you must come with me to the back.
Lavatory?
We'll, you'll need to find another place
because my pregnant wife is there.
Go through there...
go.
It will really take a while.
Baby? How are you doing in there?
Ahhh... sorry, go ahead.
Take your time... take your time.
Please go ahead.
Go there, go there.
She's gone, she's gone.
Relax... relax...
Miss?
Are you okay?
Oh what to do?
There's an emergency at car 11!
Chief!
- Hello?
- Yes, Kim?
It's more serious than we anticipated.
It's not just an overnight Ansan incident.
I don't know whats happening,
but it's not a simple strike.
MILITARY DEPLOYED TO CONTROL RIOTS
- They say it's nationwide.
What about breathing?
- Hello?
But I can't seem to
control her seizure!
Sir, what should we do?
I'll call you back.
INDISCRIMINATE VIOLENCE AT RIOT
Oh no, they'll get hurt.
That's terrible.
These people are crazy!
They should be shot and killed.
You mustn't say that.
Look, look.
What's up with them?
Miss?
What must I do?
Chief? Chief where are you?
I don't believe this...
Chief?
Min Jin? Min Jin?
What is that?
What is happening?!
What is this?
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hurry! Everyone Run!
Stand up!
Conductor! We have a situation here!
Run! Run!
- Oh my god!
- What the hell?!
Get away! Just go!
Get out of here! Head for the back!
Get up! Hurry!
Daddy!
Baby?
Sang Hwa! So damn loud!
Sorry, the thing is..
Get off me!
You idiot! Go help her!
Hey!
What's with you?!
Have you gone mad?!
Baby?
Sung-Gyeong!
You can run, right?
MASSIVE VIOLENCE, INCREASING CASUALTIES
Get away!
Get the door! The door!
Shut the door!
Quick!
Shut it!
Shut it now!
Just shut it!
I know him!
Where's the lock?
Buddy! How do I lock this?
Do you hear me?!
Let it go.
What?
I don't think they know how to open it.
They attack because they see us.
What in the...
What are they?
Soo-an, you okay?
Hey buddy.
What is it?
Don't you owe me an apology?
What do you mean?
Look at this chump.
You shut the door in our faces, asshole!
You weren't the only ones in danger!
What a piece of work.
Come here.
I'll feed you to them.
Stop it!
Everyone's just scared.
Attention please!
Due to our current situation,
we won't be stopping in Cheonan.
For your safety,
please stay in your seats.
Hello? Anyone there?
Yes, go ahead.
Do you even know
what's going on back here?
Why aren't you stopping in Cheonan?
We're aware, sir.
This is an order from the control center.
Please be seated.
That's nonsense!
People are going rabid!
Stop in Cheonan, get it?!
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry,
but could she sit down?
She's pregnant.
Okay.
Sit, sit.
Thank you.
MOTHER
Yes mom?
Are you on your way?
Yes, we're en route.
Where are you?
Why is it so loud?
What's happening? Everyone's fighting.
Are you and Soo-an okay?
Why're you breathing like that,
are you hurt?
Seok-Woo, my baby.
Please take care of Soo-an.
Mom, you okay?
My dear Soo-an...
I love her so much,
but she only wants her mom...
That bitch!
Mom?
Dad.
Dad!
Is granny okay?
What the hell?
Soo-an, sit down.
My fellow citizens,
we're currently experiencing
violent riots in all major cities,
resulting in many civilians and police injuries.
Riots led to shutting down of various districts,
and the rioters have forcibly attempted to destroy
and take over government property,
For this reason,
we're entering state of emergency
in order to control current situations.
Thanks to our government's rapid response,
various outbreaks are being contained.
Fellow citizens,
please refrain from reacting to baseless rumors,
and stay in the safety of your homes.
We must stay calm and trust the government,
in order to overcome such trying obstacle.
We believe that your safety is not in jeopardy.
ANALYST KIM
Mommy's phone is off.
Those in front, hurry up!
Soo-an, sit over here.
Don't worry, I'll give her a call.
Jong-Gil, come sit down.
You're older, you sit down.
I'm fine, take it.
Baby, let's go over there.
Ma'am, take my seat.
- I'm okay.
- No, please sit.
Child.
Would you like one?
Thank you.
What a great kid.
- We both got seats.
- Keep walking.
That bag...
Soo-an, you didn't have to do that.
- Do what?
- Being good.
At a time like this,
only watch out for yourself.
Answer me.
Granny always had knee aches.
Soo-an...
May I have your attention please.
Our train will conclude service at Daejeon station.
Military is deployed there,
and will secure our train.
So once we arrive, please exit the train.
I repeat,
Daejeon station is our last stop.
Which cities can be entered?
Yeosu, Uljin, Busan.
What about Daejeon?
Excuse me, I need to use it.
Why not?!
Soo-an, stay put.
Hey, kiddo.
Yes?
Who is he? Your dad?
Yes.
- Real dad?
- Yes.
I wanna know.
What does he do?
He's a fund manager.
- Fund manager?
- Yes.
He's a bloodsucker, a bloodsucker
He leaches off others.
Don't say that in front of his child.
It's okay.
That's what everyone thinks.
Want some?
It's what Sleepy eats.
This is Sleepy. Say hello
Baby's name is Sleepy?
No, the fetus name.
It's like a nickname,
her dad is too lazy to
come up with a name yet.
Touch her belly.
Right here.
Go on.
Felt it?
I made that.
- You idiot...
- But it's true. No?
Mr. Seok, you called me at a bad time.
Wait, wait!
Let me ask you something.
What?
I'm on KTX to Daejeon.
KTX? Right this minute?
Yes, I'm almost there.
Is it true the military is deployed in Daejeon?
Yes, that's correct.
Is that so? It must be safe there.
Well... it's...
Min, it is safe, right?
Once you arrive, you'll be quarantined.
What?
I'm with my daughter.
Can you help me and my daughter, huh?
But the thing is...
I'll get you a real scoop,
do me a favor.
Don't go to the main square,
come to the East one, okay?
I'll let my men know.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks so much.
All dead...
What's going on?
So quiet...
Is it Daejeon?
There's nobody.
Why isn't anyone here?
Out of my way.
What's going on back there?
This is that violent incident I told you about!
Conductor!
- You're the conductor?
- Yes.
How many can fit in the engine car?
We must uncouple it and go to Busan.
- Uncouple?
- Yes!
- We can't!
- Why not?!
It can't be done here.
Then where's the military?
Yeah right.
I only received a report about it...
Where's my business card?
I'm the COO of Stallion Express,
all routes into Daejeon are cut off.
Our buses are all rerouted.
But what for?
The city's been quarantined!
They probably won't let us in.
But Busan is still open,
so let's go there!
Wait, if that's true...
- we must take others.
- Take who?!
Let's check the station first.
Hey!
RESTRICTED AREA
Don't mind them.
Come on Soo-an.
Where are we going?
We're going this way.
- Just us?
- Yes, let's go.
What is it?
I'm going this way too.
Main square is that way,
just follow the others.
I'm gonna come with you.
I heard your phone call.
About pulling you two out.
I know others will be quarantined.
It's not true, Soo-an.
I'll go tell the others.
- Soo-an, you don't have to.
- Of course I do!
Forget them!
We're all on our own!
Dad, you only care about yourself.
That's why mommy left.
Soo-an...
Hey!
Here! Over here!
Please help!
Soo-an, stay right here.
Goddamit!
Hold on!
Go back up! Go! Go!
Mr. Min...
- Mr. Seok!
- I'm in Daejeon.
Is everything okay there?
I can't contact my men!
What?
Hello?!
Help me...
Come on! Hurry!
Hurry up! Quick!
Take this!
Run! Come on!
Asshole! Come on!
Faster!
Hold them off!
- Over here! Run!
- This way! Hurry!
Here! Here!
This way!
Come on!
Hurry!
Why aren't we leaving yet?!
There are still more people!
Hurry up!
Come this way!
Hurry!
Faster! Here!
Granny!
Please get up!
No, stop!
My sister!
Hop on!
Me too!
Let me in!
Please!
How much longer?
We have to leave!
No! my friends aren't here yet!
Those onboard must survive!
Am I right?
Conductor.
Please... depart.
Run! Let's go!
Look, the train!
Run faster!
Snap out of it, idiot!
Watch out!
Control, 101 could not dock
at Daejeon due to the outbreak.
Advise which station is available to dock, over.
101, due to unstable comm,
it is difficult to advise.
Control, is 101 clear to reach Busan? Over.
101, we'll clear your route to Busan.
Control center, out.
Advise when you make contact with Busan.
101, out.
Attention everyone.
For those safety of those on board,
we'll head straight for Busan.
We won't be making any stops.
Conductor, can you hear me?
Go ahead.
Were you able to contact Busan?
No, the communication is erratic.
Full speed, no matter what!
Or we won't get in, understand?!
Young-Gook, where are you?!
I thought you were dead!
I'm sorry!
No one else made it!
I'm sorry.
- Baby?
- Mister!
Why are you answering?
Where are you?
We're, we're in the train washroom!
Washroom? Which car?
Well... it's...
Car 13!
- Get your ass over here!
- Baby!
Was that my kid?
Is she okay?
Washroom in car 13.
Gonna pass through?
Let's say you got through and rescue them,
how will you come back?
In car 15,
people are gathered there.
CAR 9
Only 4 cars away.
I'll lead.
You in the middle,
and you in the back.
Block anyone attacking from the rear.
I heard you're a fund manager.
Then you're an expert,
at leaving useless people behind.
Wait till we exit the tunnel.
Let's go.
Come on!
Let's go!
Move.
Out of the way.
They stopped once we entered the tunnel, right?
Probably because of the darkness.
Yeah, I think so too.
There are even more here.
What do we do now?
There's no way around it.
Let's go.
Hey, can I borrow your cell?
Get that out of my face.
Yo, douche.
Felt good to see
your kid thanks to me, huh?
Are you grateful or what?
Why is your ringtone so tacky?
What's wrong with it?
How do I change it?
Am I funny?
You little rat.
How tall are you?
181cm.
10km away, at 300km/h...
What?
2 minutes... upcoming tunnel
will give us 2 minutes.
- Can we do it?
- We gotta, we gotta...
If we miss this one,
there's another in 3km...
I bet you never get to
play with your daughter.
When she gets older,
she'll understand why you work so hard.
Dads get all the bad rap and no praise,
but it's all about sacrifice, right?
What's with the look?
Did I sound cool?
People rescued.
Heading over now.
My friend's coming here!
What did you say?
My friend from another car is coming over.
- Who's coming?
- My friend!
He was in car 9,
and he rescued some people.
Rescued?
From there to here,
passing through those monsters?
Without any injuries?
You sure they're not infected?
Are you damn sure?!
What do you mean?
Look, look at them.
At a moment like this,
no one knows what
happened to their families.
We don't even know if
your damn friends are infected!
But allow them in here?! Huh?!
I don't believe this.
Sir,
please say something.
They'll be here soon.
Sir!
Get over here.
One!
Two!
Run!
Jin-Hee! Jin-Hee!
Hurry the hell up!
Open up!
Hey! Open this door!
Jin-hee!
Open this door!
- Open up!
- Jin-Hee! Jin-Hee!
Open it now!
It won't budge!
I can't open it!
Smash it!
Stand back!
Hurry up!
Dammit!
You stupid idiots!
Come on!
In-Gil!
Young-Gook!
Stand back!
Stay away!
Stay back, baby.
Please go!
Buddy, hey!
Take her and leave.
You have to go!
I said go, douche!
I'm getting tired, please go.
- Please take...
- ...care of her. I will.
I'll hold them off, just go!
I'm... I'm sorry.
We have to go, let's go!
Yoon Su-yun!
Our baby's name!
Got it?
Why did you do it?!
You bastard!
We could've save them!
Why?!
He's infected!
He's one of them!
This guy's infected!
His eyes! Look at his eyes!
He'll become one of them!
Do you all want to die?!
We must throw them out!
Those of you who just arrived,
I don't think you can stay with us.
Please move to the vestibule.
Just go!
Get out!
Get out now!
Hurry up!
Move!
Go!
Leave us!
Get the hell out!
Out now!
Hurry!
It'll be safer for you to stay here.
No, I don't want to stay.
I'm coming with you.
But...
Get the hell out!
What are you waiting for!
Okay, let's go.
Get out! Rest of you!
Get out!
Get out of here!
Let's go.
Tie it faster!
More ties! Neckties!
Shut up! I'm working on it!
Yun In-Gil
Great name.
Always helping others
instead of yourself.
Why did you live like that?
What was the point?
So stupid...
Shut up! Be quiet!
Stay in your seat!
What a load of shit.
Finish up and do the other side too.
Thank you for everyting.
That woman...
Stop her!
Control, this is Busan-bound 101!
Requesting current situation in Busan, over.
Control?!
Control!
It's your birthday...
Don't worry.
I'll take you to mom no matter what.
Aren't you scared?
Of course I am.
I'm scared too.
I was so scared.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I practiced that song just for you.
That's why I couldn't sing.
Because I didn't see you.
Will you stay with me?
EX-WIFE
The person you're calling is not available.
ANALYST KIM
Yes, Kim.
Have you arrived in Busan?
Not yet, where are you?
Is it okay there?
Busan succeeded in initial defense.
What?
Are you sure?
Where did you hear that news, huh?
Boss...
all of this started at YT BioTech.
It's our project!
Our plant started all of this!
Boss...
please tell me it's not our fault, eh?
We're only doing our jobs, right?
Is this my fault, huh?
It's...
It's not your fault.
Thank you...
Kim...
Attention please.
Due to a blockage on our track,
we have stopped at East Daegu Station.
We should either wait for the rescue team,
or we'll have to reach Busan in another train.
As soon as I end this announcement,
I will find a working train
and put it on the left most track.
What's going on?
I repeat, left most track.
If you're alive,
please transfer safely.
Godspeed.
Will there be a rescue?
I heard that Busan is safe.
We have to move now.
Coast clear?
Yeah.
You go ahead.
We've have to find a way across.
What in the...
Over here!
No...
Oh no...
What now!
We have to move, come on!
Jin-Hee, let's go!
Stand back!
Jin-Hee!
This can't be...
I'm sorry...
Daddy! Wake up!
Daddy! Daddy!
What's going on?
Come on faster! Faster!
Faster!
Dammit!
Help!
Soo-an, come here!
Soo-an, Soo-an!
Mister!
Soo-an!
Soo-an, come here!
Mister...
Go! Hurry!
Come on!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Hurry! Hurry!
Daddy!
Mister.
Please bring me to Busan.
Please help me.
Please... please...
My mother is waiting for me.
Please bring me home.
giving his address
Please save me.
You're...
...already infected.
No.
No, no,
no... no...
Soo-an come here
Sit here.
Listen to me...
Here is the throttle,
the brakes.
When you need to stop,
pull the brakes.
Soo-an...
Look at me...
look at me, Soo-an.
Look at me, look at me...
Soo-an...
listen to me.
You must stay with her, okay?
Busan is still safe.
- That is why... that is why...
- Don't go!
Don't go, father!
Come with us.
Please don't leave me...
Don't go...
come with us.
You should come with us.
Don't go...
Please come with us, don't go...
Don't go! Don't go!
Daddy! Daddy!!
Don't go!!
Daddy!!
Daddy!! No don't go!!
Daddy!!! Daddy!!!
I see something.
Two subjects are approaching at our location.
Looks like a woman and a child.
Are you able to verify the subjects?
Over.
It's so dark on the other side.
I can't see them clearly.
Cant see the subjects clearly.
Unable to verify.
Kill them.
Over.
Two survivors approaching!
--THE END--